<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>bash on jb</title>
    <link>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/tags/bash/</link>
    <description>Recent content in bash on jb</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>This work is licensed under a Creative Commons Attribution-NonCommercial 4.0 International License.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 10:04:47 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/tags/bash/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>THM_PickleRick_Walkthrough</title>
      <link>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/posts/2023/04/thm_picklerick_walkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Apr 2023 10:04:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/posts/2023/04/thm_picklerick_walkthrough/</guid>
      <description>Pickle Rick TryHackMe performed by: jb-williams Pickle Rick To access the box add the machines IP to this https://&amp;lt;IP&amp;gt;.p.thmlabs.com
Traveling to the sight we can start gathering information First it is always good to View Page Source to see if there are any information disclosers accidently left in the html source code. Doing so, you can see that a comment left in the source code is reminding Rick that the user name for their account is R1ckRul3s Now we scan the box with nmap to see what info we can gather.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My_Usb_Encrypton_Process</title>
      <link>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/posts/2022/08/my_usb_encrypton_process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 16:43:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/posts/2022/08/my_usb_encrypton_process/</guid>
      <description>LUKS USB Encryption for Linux performed by: jb-williams This is the process I use to partition and encrypt usb drives.
I have not tested tested it on anything other than usb&amp;rsquo;s, though a similar process would potentially work. !! Notice !! Running these commands on the wrong drive could Erase All Data on that Drive!!
Only Recoverable if You Had a Backup Make sure you know: Device Name(ie: /dev/sdb) Device Size(ie: 15GiB) REQS:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brightxf</title>
      <link>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/posts/2022/08/brightxf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Aug 2022 11:59:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jb-williams.github.io/jbtech.github.io/posts/2022/08/brightxf/</guid>
      <description>Brightxf performed by: jb-williams !! Run at Own Risk !!
No issues have come from my use of these but that doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean there won&amp;rsquo;t be I enjoy making/finding the most minimal gui and still be functional as a daily-driver(functional specifically to my needs). I tend to prefer cwm, a simple window manager, and sxhkd, used as a hot-key daemon, and I test my setup on several different laptops of different specs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
